And now, Freddie will read
the next question.
- Sent to us at iCarly.com.
- Freddie?
Dear Carly,
Don't you think it would be awesome
to be Freddie's girlfriend?"
Read the real question.
"Dear Carly, what would
you and Sam look like
if you had purple troll hair?"
Hmm.
What would Sam and I look like
if we had purple troll hair?
I guess the only way to find
out is to look at the monitor.
Now, before we go tonight,
we're gonna get serious.
Freddie, the serious lights.
As you all know, one of the best
shows on TV is "America sings."
And tomorrow night, a new
champion will be chosen by you,
the American public.
Now, the best singer by far is--
but all the polls and blogs
say that David's gonna
lose to his opponent.
Wade Collins.
And we can't let that happen.
So you gotta vote for David.
Come on, people.
Whip out your phones and votes.
We really want David to win.
It's all I want.
It's all I want, too.
It's what all the cool kids want.
And trolls!
Vote for David Archuleta.
Vote for David.
I'm a troll.
Vote for David Archuleta.
Vote for David.
Unh!
In five, four, three, two-- [Music]
I know, you'll see
somehow the world
will change for me
and be so wonderful
live life, breathe air
and feel so wonderful
it's all for real
I'm telling you
just how I feel
so wake up the members
of my nation
it's your time to be
there's no chance
unless you take one
there'll be time to see
the brighter side
of every situation
some things are meant to be
so give me your best
and leave the rest to me
okay, check out this application
I downloaded on my pear phone.
It makes all the little--
aww, she licked my phone.
Shh! "America sings"
is coming back on.
Never lick my phone again.
She did it again.
Freddie, be quiet.
Sam, stop licking technology.
And it all comes down to
tonight-- the final moment.
The winner of "America sings"
is going to be one of these
two amazing artists-- David!
David! David!
He's not gonna win.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Your votes are in and they've
been counted and the winner
of "America sings"
will be announced right after this.
Augh!
Another commercial?
And they wonder why they're
losing teens to the Internet.
Carly! Carly!
Have you seen my copy of that movie
"boogie bear takes Manhattan"?
No. When did you lose it?
A little over 10 years ago.
10 years?
Yeah. I just got this
letter from video village
telling me I never returned it.
So?
So it's a dollar for
every day it's late.
They're saying I owe
them over 3,600 bucks.
So just go to the place and
tell them you returned it
10 years ago.
What, lie?
Yeah.
Oh, no, I can't.
I'm a terrible liar.
Its true.
One time-- don't tell the story.
I'm telling the story.
One time we were gonna ride
roller coasters on a school day,
and when Spencer came to
get me, he told Ms. Briggs
he was taking me to the doctor
and she said, "which one?"
And Spencer said--
Dr. roller coaster.
And guess what I didn't
get to ride that day?
You know, I can teach you to lie.
Yeah? I don't think so.
Why not?
If you wanna be good at something,
you might as well learn
from the best.
Yeah, I got third place
in the Washington state
lying competition.
Yeah, but still, I don't
think--whoa, third?
Dude, I'm lying.
Impressive.
Okay, so you wanna start tomorrow?
Oh, I can't tomorrow.
I gotta go to my
great-uncle's funeral.
Oh, man, I'm so sorry.
Lying!
Fantastic.
Shh! It's back on.
Welcome back.
All right.
I've kept you and Wade
Collins and David Archuleta
waiting long enough.
America voted.
And the winner of this year's
"America sings" competition is--
come on, David.
Please be Archuleta.
Say it.
David Archuleta.
[Squealing and shrieking]
Oh, yes.
I can't believe it.
This is unbelievable.
That's why I can't believe it.
Oh, David!
He won!
Yeah. Yeah, he won.
Go David! Archuleta! Go!
Found it!
Your movie?
No, my little banjo.
[Music]
Yo. Yo. Yo. Yo.
Okay. Ready?
Watch the TV swing out.
What?
I fixed it so it swings out
18 percent faster now.
Okay, you've gotta get a girlfriend.
I know.
Uh-- no.
Yeah.
Turn on the TV.
They're talking about "iCarly."
Turn on channel nine. Hurry!
Whoa, cool yo-yo.
Turn on channel nine.
Many were surprised that Wade
Collins lost, and according
to industry insiders David
archuleta may owe his victory
to a popular Web show
called "iCarly."
What?
No way!
Where'd you get this yo-yo?
Spencer!
Apparently the teenage
girls who host "iCarly"
told their fans to vote for archuleta.
"America sings" producer, Stan Berman,
confirmed there was a huge
spike in votes for archuleta
just after the "iCarly"
Web show.
He won because of us.
Well, we didn't do anything wrong.
We like archuleta, so
we helped him win.
Yeah.
I guess nobody got hurt.
Except that poor guy you made lose.
Look, I gotta give it up to David.
I mean, he's a great
singer, but, yeah,
it would've been nice to win.
You see, my mother's been ill,
and I was going to use the money
from the recording contract
to help her get the surgery
she needs.
Aw, his mother needs surgery.
She's not gettin' it now.
Oh, man, I forgot.
The winner gets a big recording
contract for a ton of money.
Yeah, I hear the loser gets nothing.
Hey, we used the power of "iCarly"
to help archuleta.
I know that.
So let's use "iCarly"
to help Collins.
We can bring him on, have him sing.
And Sam and I can be all "aah!
Wade Collins,"
and then maybe that'll help him
get more popular and he can get
a recording contract too.
Perfect.
I'll look up his fan site
and shoot him an e-mail.
Do it!
Someone broke your yo-yo.
I think you need to go downstairs.
Hey, look, I returned the movie.
[Electronic warbling]
Well, I don't care
what your records say.
I know I returned it.
When?
Well, you know, like 10 years
ago, on Thurs--Wednes--
it was an afternoon.
That's when--okay, I'm
lying, I'm a dirty liar.
These are the eyes of a liar.
[Knock on door]
Spencer!
Hey, you're an hour late.
I know. I got jumped.
What?
I was on my way here when
these two huge biker chicks
jumped out of an alley, beat
me up and stole my backpack.
Ohmigod, are you all right?
No!
I better call the cops.
Okay, and when you get 'em on the
phone, make sure you tell 'em
that I'm lying.
Right.
Hey, my little sister's friend
just got-- I'll call you back.
You make it look so easy.
Just takes practice.
Yeah, but I don't know if I
have your talent for this.
Dude, lying is easy.
You just gotta say
stuff like it's true,
like you really mean it.
You can learn this.
You think?
Yeah, you're smart.
Thanks.
Wait. Was that a lie?
No.
I think you're really smart.
Okay, as you know, Wade
Collins was supposed to be
here on "iCarly" tonight to
sing for us, but apparently
Freddie screwed up.
He said he would be here.
Anyway, since Wade isn't
here-- our little friend Gibby
is gonna come out and sing for you.
Get out here, Gibby.
Oh, yeah.
Hey there!
When I wake up in the middle
of the night screaming,
this is the song my mom sings
to calm me down. Freddie?
[Beep]
[Music]
My screaming little angel
don't you cry
my screaming little angel--
cut the song!
Hey, you guys, he's here.
Say hello to-- the first
runner-up from "America sings"--
so thanks for comin' on the show.
Yeah.
Well, thank you for having me.
I'm a huge fan of
"iCarly"-- and apparently
so are a lot of people.
Yeah.
We're sorry we influenced the voting.
And, you know, kinda ruined your life.
Oh, no worries, you
didn't ruin my life.
You just ruined a big part of it.
Well, we're really psyched
that you took time
out of your busy schedule
to be with us here tonight.
Um, actually, I'm not all that busy.
But I thought you shoot a music video
after being on "America sings."
No, no. Only the winner
gets to do a music video.
I lost.
So, you didn't get anything
for coming in second?
No, I did.
They gave me a jacket and a gift
certificate to b.F. Wang's.
Oh.
I love their cashew chicken.
Oh, yeah, me too.
Yeah, it's great. Chicken.
Hey, am I gonna sing or what?
No.
Gibby.
Hey, you know what?
What's that?
Freddie's awesome with
a camera, so how about
you let us help you
make a music video?
Yeah, good call.
And we can premiere it
right here on "iCarly."
Totally.
Seriously?
Sure.
Why not?
Let's do it.
Oh, thanks.
You guys are the best!
Okay, Freddie's giving us
that signal, which means--
show's over.
But be sure to check out the next
"iCarly"-- for the premiere of
Wade Collins' new music video.
Until then, always remember--
never forget-- what was it?
I forget.
Me too. Oh, man.
That's embarrassing.
Wow.
Bye.
See ya.
Later!
And we're clear.
Okay, way to go, Wade.
Yeah, nice job, Wade.
Hey, my friends call me Wade.
You call me Mr. Collins.
Um, okay, I thought
we were friends here.
Why would I be friends with
a group of teenage idiots
who destroyed my singing career?
Okay.
So you don't wanna do the video?
Augh! Don't be stupid!
Of course we're doing the video.
It's the least you
sprags can do for me.
Did he just call me stupid?
I heard "sprags."
I'll come over tomorrow and
we'll shoot the video then.
Okay. What time?
When I get here.
Oh, and I'll need a
personal assistant, you.
Yes!
Wade Collins is leaving.
What a jerk!
I hate him.
We have to make a music
video for that guy?
Sweet! My first chest hair!
[Gasps] Ow.
[Music]
Um, Wade?
It's noon, and we haven't
shot anything yet.
Are you almost ready?
Mr. Collins doesn't want you
to talk to him directly.
Fine, just tell him what I said.
Okay. Mr. Collins-- tell the director
I'll be ready when I'm ready
and to get out of my face.
Sure thing.
Um-- yeah, yeah.
Hey, do you think this dress
is a little too saucy?
It's a music video.
You need to look hotter
than you usually do.
Well, thank you.
Where's Sam?
She saw the dress you
wanted her to wear,
threw a corn dog at
it, and walked out.
Ah.
But the other girls are here.
Ohh, hello, other girls.
Is Wade ready?
I don't know.
He's been making Gibby brush
his hair for 45 minutes.
You've got beautiful hair.
Don't look at it!
He's such a nub.
I don't wanna do this anymore.
We have to.
His mom needs surgery,
and if it weren't for us
he'd have a big record deal and
lots of money, and stop drooling
over those girls.
Wade, come on, we gotta do this.
I need you up on the hood of the car.
Uh, Mr. Collins, he wants you
up on the hood of the car.
Thank you, Jibley.
His name is Gibby.
You can call me Jibley.
Okay, Carly, I need you
and the other girls
to get around the car
there and look awesome.
I'll try my best.
Okay, Wade, Gibby's
gonna cue the music,
and when I yell action--
just roll the camera!
Action!
[Music]
Hey, check out this little guy!
Jibley, stop the music!
Aww! He's so cute!
Where'd you get him?
You know the lady downstairs in 4-g?
The one whose gums
are always bleeding?
Yeah.
Hey!
Did we just stop shooting
Wade Collins' music video
because of a stupid animal?
He's not stupid.
He's adorable.
Look at his little--
no, I hate puppies.
I swear, you're all just
a bunch of hob-knockers.
Hob-knockers?
I'm going down to get some yogg-urt.
Yogg-urt?
Um, we're in the middle of
shooting your music video.
No, you're all busy worshipping
a filthy little beast.
Ucch! Why are all
Americans such idiots?
I thought we were hob-knockers.
Ooh.
Aahhh.
Ehh.
Ooh-aaah.
Come on.
I don't know if I can do this.
You can. Let's go.
But what if I--oh.
Let's go. Like we practiced.
Start.
Hello, I'm Spencer shay.
You guys sent me this letter
saying I never returned
"boogie bear takes Manhattan."
That's right, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
When?
10 years ago.
How can you remember that?
'Cause I brought it
back the same day I won
my Olympic silver medal.
You won a silver medal?
Sure did.
For what?
Luge.
Where's the medal?
At my summer home in Prague.
When were you there last?
March 3rd.
I had lunch there with the pope.
You're friends with the pope?
He's my cousin.
What's his e-mail address?
Pontiff-one@pope.org.
And you're sure you brought
that movie back here?
Yes. Now I have to go.
I'm going horseback
riding with a supermodel.
Spencer?
Yeah?
You're ready.
I know.
I always cry
when you're not around
you make me weep
when you're gone
you make me sing
this sad song
you make me cry
[lion roars]
[Lion roars]
Wow.
You made Wade look awesome.
Good video, Fredison.
Thanks.
It was hard to find good footage
of the guy not screaming at me
and calling me an
untalented hob-knocker.
What is a hob-knocker?
Oh! That's gross!
And illegal.
I hate Wade Collins.
Well, at least the video's done.
We'll give it to Wade, and then
he's out of our lives forever.
Good.
Not soon enough.
Come on, I need to shoot
video of your heads
for that "iCarly" bit.
What bit?
The one where we dance
inside each other's mouths.
Oh, right, random mouth dancing.
Right, open wide and-- rolling.
Ahh!
I'm here for my music video.
Who let you up here?
We're in the middle of something.
Yeah, yeah, you can get
back to your obnoxious
little comedy show after
you give me my video.
Look, you little-- Sam.
Just give him the video.
Whatever.
Hob-knocker.
Um, is that any way to
talk around my mum?
Your mum?
Ha ha.
Wait, this is your mother?
Hello, love.
On "America sings,"
you said your mother was gravely
ill and needed surgery.
Yeah, I said that to get sympathy.
You silly Americans are
suckers for a good sob story.
Whoops, mum!
You got six months to live.
Blimey!
Here!
Just take your video and go.
No!
You're the one who
said we owed this guy.
Yeah, well, not anymore!
You know, I felt guilty using "iCarly"
to help David archuleta win.
But now I know we did the right thing.
You didn't deserve to win.
Give me my video!
Hey!
Get her, mum!
Aah! Aah!
Get her off! Get her off!
Blimey!
Excuse me, miss?
What's up?
I received this letter
from your store claiming
that I never returned my copy of
"boogie bear takes Manhattan."
Oh, yeah. When was it due?
10 years ago.
Yikes. You're a little late.
No, because I did return the video.
Oh, you did?
No, I'm sorry!
I didn't return the video!
I watched it at my buddy Socko's
house and his mom got mad
because we spilled gravy on her
carpet and she threw me out
and I thought I left the
video there, but I didn't.
He says I didn't and I thought I did
and I looked for it everywhere
and I'm sorry, I don't--
I didn't mean to lie.
I don't like lying.
I don't like the way it feels.
And you know I tell my
sister, uh, don't lie.
I tell my little sister
you shouldn't lie.
It's not good. It's bad.
I--I--honesty is the
best policy, right?
But, you know, Sam, her friend,
was telling me how to lie
and that makes me nauseous and I
feel queasy and I don't feel--
dude, my boss just sends those
letters out to scare people.
He does?
That's not cool.
I'll just take it out of the computer.
No worries.
Swear?
Yeah.
You're very nice.
You're very-- cute.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Wanna visit my summer home in
Prague and meet my cousin the pope?
Yeah, I knew you'd giggle.
And now Freddie will
read the next question--
sent in to us at iCarly.com.
Fredderly?
"Dear Carly and Sam, "do you
guys ever work out at a gym?"
Excellent question.
We did work out at a gym last summer.
Freddie, can you cue the video of
me and Carls from last summer?
Sure will.
[Grunting]
We're bodybuilders.
Look how big our muscles are.
You wish you were us.
[Both grunting]
We're superhumans.
Okay, last week we
promised to show you guys
an original Wade Collins music video.
But then we learned that Wade
Collins is a big ol' jerk-face.
A raging jerk-a-holic.
Worst guy ever.
We hate him with all our hearts.
He's a bad dude.
But if you don't believe
us-- take it from someone
who's worked closely with
him on "America sings."
Look out, people, 'cause
here comes-- Whoo!
Hi.
Hey, David.
Archuleta!
Thanks for comin'
on the show.
Well, thanks for having me.
I'm a huge fan of "iCarly."
Who isn't?
Uh, losers.
Exactly.
So, David, what was it like
hangin' out with Wade Collins?
Oh, well, you know, he's okay.
You don't like him, do you?
Not really. No.
Let it out, David.
Well, he called me a hob-knocker.
I don't even know what that means.
Oh, gross!
And illegal.
The important thing is we all agree
that Wade Collins is horrible.
But just in case you don't
believe me, Carly, or David--
please enjoy this little
video Freddie put together.
Freddie, roll the video.
Happy to, Carly.
[Music]
I wanted tuna fish!
[Hacking]
[Spits]
I've got a pimple in my ear.
Too hot--hot--hot!
I'm sorry.
You're a stupid American,
Freddie, stupid American.
[Spits]
Ah-choo!
You're a bunch of
stupid American girls!
You bunch of hob-knockers!
I don't care about music!
I want money!
[Spits]
Hob-hob-hob-knocker!
I have to look beautiful!
Jibley!
Unngh!
I hate children!
I hate teenagers!
I hate animals!
And I hate America!
Isn't he charming?
Now, if you're an American
and you found some
of Wade's comments offensive--
and you'd like to have
a little chat with him
about it-- he's staying
at the Chambrulay hotel,
right here in Seattle.
721 Baker street.
Should we tell 'em what room?
I don't think we should.
Room 513.
That's 5-1-3.
And remember, if you're an
American-- he hates you--
and thinks you can't beat him up.
Okay, before we go-- you guys
wanna hear David archuleta sing?
[Cheers and applause]
Well, he's not gonna!
Sore throat, sorry.
But we do have some good
music for you guys.
Please enjoy my brother Spencer
who's gonna play us out
on his little banjo.
[Applause]
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0